Guide to the John Franklin Enders Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence and Topical Files, 1916-1988; Series I; 36.75' (88 boxes)
  - Nason, Mary M., 1959-1962, 1965-1967 (Box 58, Folder 1365)
  - National Academy of Sciences
    - General, 1952-1954 April (Box 58, Folder 1366-1367)
    - General, 1954 May-1969, undated (Box 59, Folder 1368-1383)
    - General, 1970-1975 (Box 60, Folder 1384-1385)
    - Proceedings, 1968, 1970, 1973-1980, undated (Box 60, Folder 1386-1388)
    - Proposals for nominations, undated (Box 60, Folder 1389)
  - National Agricultural College, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 1390)
  - National Cancer Institute
    See: box 12, folders 246-251
  - National Cancer Institute: meeting on DNA viruses, 1966, undated (Box 60, Folder 1391)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1966-1967, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 1392)
  - National Cyclopedia of American, Biography, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 1393)
  - National Drug Company, 1959, 1962-1964 (Box 60, Folder 1394)
  - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis
    - Budget figures, 1948-1957, undated (Box 60, Folder 1395-1397)
    - Committee on Immunization: proceedings, 1951 (Box 60, Folder 1398)
    - Complement fixation conference, 1954, undated (Box 61, Folder 1399)
    - Correspondence, general, 1942-1959 (Box 61, Folder 1400-1409)
    - Correspondence, general, 1960-1965,1974 (Box 62, Folder 1410-1412)
    - ECHO Viruses Committee, 1955-1957 September (Box 62, Folder 1413-1417)
    - Enterovirus Committee (formerly ECHO Viruses Committee), 1957 October-December (Box 62, Folder 1418)
    - Enterovirus Committee, 1958 January-December (Box 62, Folder 1419-1420)
    - Enterovirus Committee, 1959-1962, undated (Box 63, Folder 1421-1427)
    - Grant progress reports, 1949-1958 (Box 63, Folder 1428)
    - Hall of Fame, 1957-1959 undated (Box 63, Folder 1429)
    - Immunization Committee, 1951-1953 undated (Box 63, Folder 1430)
    - In Vitro Diagnostic Tests for Poliomyelitis Conference, 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 1431)
    - Neutralization Tests and Orphan Viruses Conference, 1955, undated (Box 64, Folder 1432)
    - Polio television business, 1950-1951 (Box 64, Folder 1433)
    - Round Table Conferences, 1957-1958, undated (Box 64, Folder 1434)
    - Tissue Culture Conference, 1952 February-March 7 (A-S) (Box 64, Folder 1435)
    - Tissue Culture Conference, 1952 March 7 (T-Z)-Apr, undated (Box 64, Folder 1436)
    - Tissue culture courses, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 1437)
    - Typing committee, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 1438)
    - Vaccine program, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 1439)
  - National Foundation for Infectious Diseases, 1973-1974 (Box 64, Folder 1440)
  - National Health Council, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 1441)
  - National Institutes of Health
    General note
    See also: box 47, folder 1179 See also: box 74, folder 1646
  - National Laboratories, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 1454)
  - National Registry of Microbiologists, 1963, 1966-1967, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 1455)
  - National Research Council, 1947-1955, 1967-1969, undated (Box 65, Folder 1456-1461)
  - National Science Foundation, 1956-1964, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 1462)
  - Neefe, John R., 1944-1945 (Box 66, Folder 1463)
  - Neese, Gerhard M., 1944 (Box 66, Folder 1464)
  - Neff, John M., 1965-1972 (Box 66, Folder 1465)
  - Neill, James, 1955, 1960-1962 (Box 66, Folder 1466)
  - Nelson, Carl T., 1941-1945 (Box 66, Folder 1467)
  - Nelson, Richard J., 1949 (Box 66, Folder 1468)
  - Nelson, Thomas, 1946-1949 (Box 66, Folder 1469)
  - Nesburn, Anthony B., 1963-1971, undated (Box 66, Folder 1470)
  - Neter, Erwin, 1947, 1951, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 1471)
  - Netterberg, Robert E., 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1472)
  - Neva, Franklin A., 1949-1957, 1965, 1970, undated (Box 66, Folder 1473)
  - New England College of Pharmacy, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 1474)
  - New England Deaconess Hospital, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 1475)
  - New England Institute for Medical Research, 1966, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 1476)
  - New England-Israel Freedom Award, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 1477)
  - New England Journal of Medicine, 1936, 1941, 1945 (Box 66, Folder 1478)
  - New England Journal of Medicine, 1947, 1959-1961, 1965-1977, undated (Box 66, Folder 1479)
  - New England Ophthalmological Society, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 1480)
  - New England Postgraduate Assembly, 1959, undated (Box 66, Folder 1481)
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1953-1957, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 1482)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1951, 1954-1966, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 1483)
  - New York Botanical Garden, 1954-1955 (Box 66, Folder 1484)
  - New York Cancer Research Institute, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 1485)
  - New York Times, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 1486)
  - Niven, Janet, 1969-1971 (Box 66, Folder 1487)
  - Nobel Prize
    - General, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 1488)
    - General, 1955-1956, 1959-1977, undated (Box 67, Folder 1489-1490)
    - Letters of congratulations, 1954-1955 (Box 67, Folder 1491)
  - Norrby, Erling, 1962-1965, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 1492)
  - North American Biologicals, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 1493)
  - Northwestern University commencement, 1956 (Box 67, Folder 1494)
  - Noyes, Wilbur F., 1969-1973 (Box 67, Folder 1495)
  - Nu Sigma Nu, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 1496)
  - Nuñez-Montiel, Otto, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 1497)
  - Nungester, W. J., 1947-1951, 1955-1957, 1962, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 1498)
  - Oakes, Thomas, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 1499)
  - O'Connor, Basil, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 1500)
  - Oddo, Ferdinando G., 1953-1954, 1961, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 1501)
  - Ohio Department of Health, 1953 (Box 67, Folder 1502)
  - Okatie Farms, 1949-1959 (Box 67, Folder 1503)
  - Oker-Blom, N., 1973 (Box 67, Folder 1504)
  - Olney, John M., 1948 (Box 67, Folder 1505)
  - O'Malley, Joseph P., 1956-1957, 1961, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 1506)
  - Oncley, Lawrence, 1947-1948, 1952-1954, 1959 (Box 67, Folder 1507)
  - Orellana, Tessa, undated (Box 67, Folder 1508)
  - Ormsbee, Richard, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 1509)
  - Osborne, June E., 1962, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 1510)
  - Ottinger, Richard, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 1511)
  - Oxman, Michael, 1960-1963, 1967-1971 (Box 67, Folder 1512-1513)
  - Oxman, Michael, 1972-1976, undated (Box 68, Folder 1514-1515)
  - Page, Robertson, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 1516)
  - Palmer, Laramie, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 1517)
  - Palmer, Robert Sterling, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 1518)
  - Pan American Sanitary Bureau, 1956, 1961, 1965-1967, undated (Box 68, Folder 1519)
  - Papain: data for paper, undated (Box 68, Folder 1520)
  - Pappenheimer, Alwin M., 1942-1949, 1957, 1961, 1965, 1968, 1973, undated (Box 68, Folder 1521)
  - Parade, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 1522)
  - Parents' Magazine, 1946, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 1523)
  - Parke, Davis and Company, 1954-1956, 1959, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 1524)
  - Parker, Raymond C., 1954 (Box 68, Folder 1525)
  - Parker, Robert F., 1955 (Box 68, Folder 1526)
  - Parker, Robert P., 1949, 1956, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 1527)
  - Parkman, Robertson, undated (Box 68, Folder 1528)
  - Passano Foundation Award
    - General, 1953-1954, 1957-1961, undated (Box 68, Folder 1529)
    - Letters of congratulations, 1953-1955, undated (Box 68, Folder 1530)
  - Patch, Cephas T., 1972-1973, undated (Box 68, Folder 1531)
  - Pattyn, Stefaan R., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 1532)
  - Paul, David M., 1962 (Box 68, Folder 1533)
  - Paul, John R., 1947-1961 (Box 68, Folder 1534)
  - Paul, John R., 1963, 1966-1972, undated (Box 68, Folder 1535)
    See also: box 4, folders 80-81 See also: box 51, folder 1224
  - Paul B. Hoeber, Inc., 1942-1943 (Box 68, Folder 1536)
  - Pauling, Linus, 1957-1958, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 1537)
  - Pavan, Deborah, 1963-1964, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 1538)
  - Pavan, Reed, 1970-1974, undated (Box 69, Folder 1539)
  - Pavilanis, Victor, 1960, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 1540)
  - Pearson, H. E., 1931, 1941-1945, 1955 (Box 69, Folder 1541)
  - Pediatric Currents, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 1542)
  - Pediatrics, 1971, 1974-1975 (Box 69, Folder 1543)
  - Peebles, Paul T., 1973 (Box 69, Folder 1544)
  - Peebles, Thomas J., 1952-1959, 1963-1965, 1972, undated (Box 69, Folder 1545)
  - Pereira, H. G., 1960 (Box 69, Folder 1546)
  - Peres, Jose Noronha, 1954-1960, 1963, 1966, 1969, undated (Box 69, Folder 1547)
  - Peristalsis Club, 1949-1972, undated (Box 69, Folder 1548-1550)
  - Personal files
    - Bibliographies and vitae, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 69, Folder 1551)
    - Biographical information, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 69, Folder 1552)
    - Correspondence, 1932-1933, 1937-1942, 1946-1959 (Box 69, Folder 1553-1557)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1977, 1980-1984, 1988, undated (Box 70, Folder 1558-1569)
    - Enders State Forest, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 1570)
    - Insurance and retirement papers, 1956-1958, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 1571)
    - John F. Enders School, 1961, 1964-1965 (Box 70, Folder 1572)
    - Maps of Enders's home, 1964, undated (Box 70, Folder 1573)
    - Nuts' letters, 1948-1961 September (Box 70, Folder 1574)
    - Nuts' letters, 1961 November-1964, undated (Box 70, Folder 1575)
    - Office photograph collection: correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 71, Folder 1576)
    - Photographs
      See: box 72, folder 1605
    - Requests for photographs and autographs, 1955-1977, 1981, undated (Box 71, Folder 1577-1582)
    - Yale College biology course notebook, 1916-1917 (Box 71, Folder 1583-1584)
  - Perspectives in Biology and Medicine, 1959-1965, 1969-1971, undated (Box 71, Folder 1585)
  - Perspectives in Pediatric Virology: conference, 1958-1959, undated (Box 71, Folder 1586)
  - Perspectives in Virology: symposia, 1959-1961 (Box 71, Folder 1587)
  - Perspectives in Virology: symposia, 1961-1968, undated (Box 71, Folder 1588-1589)
  - Perspectives in Virology: symposia, 1971-1974, undated (Box 71, Folder 1590)
  - Peters, A. Theophilus, 1941 (Box 71, Folder 1591)
  - Peterson, O. H., 1942 (Box 71, Folder 1592)
  - Petitions, 1963, 1968-1975 (Box 71, Folder 1593)
  - Pette, H., 1955-1967, 1970-1972 (Box 71, Folder 1594)
  - Pfaff, Mary Louise, 1954-1955 (Box 71, Folder 1595)
  - Pfefferkorn, Elmer, 1966, 1970, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 1596)
  - Phair, John J., 1942 (Box 72, Folder 1597)
  - Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Association, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 1598)
  - Philips Roxane, 1964, undated (Box 72, Folder 1599)
  - Photographs
    - Cells, miscellaneous, 1964, undated (Box 72, Folder 1600)
    - Cells, miscellaneous, undated (Box 72, Folder 1601)
    - Cultures of polio virus in vitro, undated (Box 72, Folder 1602)
    - Effect of Brunhilde and Leon viruses on roller tube cultures of human adult uterus, 1951 (Box 72, Folder 1603)
    - Effect of Brunhilde virus on epithelial cells from human embryo, undated (Box 72, Folder 1604)
    - Enders, John Franklin: individual and group, 1954-1956, 1960, 1970-1973 (Box 72, Folder 1605)
    - Explants from flask cultures inoculated with Brunhilde polio virus, 1951 (Box 72, Folder 1606)
    - Measles television broadcast, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 1607)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 72, Folder 1608)
    - Negatives of explant exposures to polio virus, 1950-1951, undated (Box 72, Folder 1609)
    - Typing of virus in roller tubes, undated (Box 72, Folder 1610)
  - Pillemer, Louis, 1945 (Box 72, Folder 1611)
  - Pinkerton, Henry, 1950 (Box 72, Folder 1612)
  - Pizarro, Enriqueta, 1952-1955, 1960-1961, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 1613)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1963-1966 (Box 72, Folder 1614)
  - Plasma Fractionation Commission
    See also: box 26, folders 649-652 See also: box 27, folders 653-655
  - Plasma sterilization, globulin, 1950-1951, undated (Box 73, Folder 1628)
  - Plotz, Harry, 1946, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 1629)
  - Plowright, W., 1957-1960 (Box 73, Folder 1630)
  - Pöhn, H. Ph., 1962 (Box 73, Folder 1631)
  - Poins, Marcel, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 1632)
  - Poleff, Dr., 1954 (Box 73, Folder 1633)
  - Poliomyelitis
    - Concklin, Charles, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 1634)
    - Conference on Biology of Poliomyelitis, 1954-1955 (Box 73, Folder 1635)
    - Conference on Laboratory Tests for Diagnosis and Determination of Immune Status in Poliomyelitis, 1955-1956, undated (Box 73, Folder 1636)
    - Correspondence, general, 1949-1959, 1965-1966, 1969, undated (Box 73, Folder 1637-1639)
    - Diagnostic studies, 1956 (Box 73, Folder 1640)
    - Experiments, index of (Box 73, Folder 1640)
    - International Poliomyelitis Congress, 1950-1958, undated (Box 74, Folder 1641-1644)
    - Multiplication of Poliomyelitis Virus in Tissue Cultures of Monkey Testes, 1951 (Box 74, Folder 1645)
    - National Institutes of Health: special polio testing contract, 1955-1956 (Box 74, Folder 1646)
    - Pathology of Poliomyelitis, undated (Box 74, Folder 1647)
    - Poliomyelitis and globulin material, 1950-1951, undated (Box 74, Folder 1648)
    - Siamese twins, 1954-1955 (Box 74, Folder 1649)
    - Smithsonian Institution exhibit, 1957-1958 (Box 74, Folder 1650)
    - Springfield, VT outbreak, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 1651)
    - Surveillance isolation reports, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 1652)
  - Poliomyelitis vaccine
    - American Medical Association, 1959-1960, undated (Box 74, Folder 1653)
    - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1953-1962, undated (Box 74, Folder 1654-1655)
    - Data on tests for viruses in specimens of Salk Vaccine, 1955, undated (Box 75, Folder 1656)
    - Institute of Medicine report, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 1657)
    - Live virus vaccine, 1959 (Box 75, Folder 1658)
    - Massachusetts Department of Public Health. Polio Vaccine Advisory Committee, 1953-1956, 1961-1962, 1965, undated (Box 75, Folder 1659-1662)
    - Publicity, 1955-1956, 1961, undated (Box 75, Folder 1663)
    - Oral vaccine, 1960-1962, 1965, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 1664)
    - Sabin vs. O'Connor, 1949 (Box 75, Folder 1665)
    - Salk Vaccine Cutter incident and U. S. Public Health Service data, 1955-1956, undated (Box 75, Folder 1666)
    - Specifications, 1954-1956 (Box 75, Folder 1667)
    - Vaccine bill panel, 1955 (Box 75, Folder 1668)
    - Vaccine study contracts: U. S. Public Health Service, 1955-1956 (Box 75, Folder 1669)
  - Pons, Marcel W., 1961, undated (Box 76, Folder 1670)
  - Population explosion, 1962, 1965-1971, undated (Box 76, Folder 1671)
  - Pound Bill (Massachusetts Senate Bill # 315), 1956-1957, undated (Box 76, Folder 1672)
  - Prakapas, Eugene J., 1967 (Box 76, Folder 1673)
  - Protein Foundation, 1955-1961, undated (Box 76, Folder 1674)
  - Purcell, Robert H., 1974 (Box 76, Folder 1675)
  - Pusey, Nathan M., 1964, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 1676)
  - Rackemann, Francis W., 1942-1944, 1949, 1952, 1956, 1961, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 1677)
  - Rake, Geoffrey W., 1942-1949, 1953-1957, undated (Box 76, Folder 1678)
  - Ralston Purina, 1965-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1679)
  - Rammelkamp, Charles H., 1944-1945 (Box 76, Folder 1680)
  - Rand Mines, 1958, undated (Box 76, Folder 1681)
    See also: box 26, folder 633
  - Rapp, Fred, 1965-1974, undated (Box 76, Folder 1682-1683)
  - Rattell, Sidney, 1941 (Box 76, Folder 1684)
  - Raymond E. Hackett Award, 1955 (Box 76, Folder 1685)
  - Readers Digest, 1951, 1959-1962, 1965-1966, undated (Box 76, Folder 1686)
  - Reid, Duncan, 1947, 1950, 1954, 1963-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1687)
  - Reid, Duncan, 1970-1974, undated (Box 76, Folder 1688)
  - Reid, Roger, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 1689)
  - Relova, Rogelio, 1957, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 1690)
  - Research and Development Board, 1947-1948 (Box 76, Folder 1691)
  - Research fellowships income tax data, 1949, 1957-1962, undated (Box 77, Folder 1692)
  - Revco, 1969, undated (Box 77, Folder 1693)
  - Reznikoff, Catherine Armstrong, 1967-1978, undated (Box 77, Folder 1694-1696)
  - Rhode Island Medical Society, 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 1697)
  - Rhodes, A. J., 1949-1956, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 1698)
  - Ribback, Richard, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 1699)
  - Rice, Warner G., 1927, 1930-1934, 1969, 1974-1975 (Box 77, Folder 1700)
  - Riggs, Austin F., 1945 (Box 77, Folder 1701)
  - Rivers, Thomas M., 1933, 1939, 1946-1947, 1951-1952, 1956-1957, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 1702)
  - Robbins, Frederick C., 1947-1974 (Box 77, Folder 1703-1705)
  - Robbins, Frederick C., 1977-1983 (Box 77, Folder 1706-1707)
  - Robbins, Frederick C., 1987, undated (Box 78, Folder 1708)
  - Robbins, H. A., 1948 (Box 78, Folder 1709)
  - Robbins, Mary Lou, 1949-1951, undated (Box 78, Folder 1710)
  - Robbins, William J., 1946-1947, 1950, 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 1711)
  - Robert Koch Foundation, 1962-1963, undated (Box 78, Folder 1712)
  - Roberts, E. C., 1942 (Box 78, Folder 1713)
  - Robinson, Charles R., 1969-1972, 1978, undated (Box 78, Folder 1714)
  - Robinson, Donald, 1971, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 1715)
  - Robinson, Elliot, 1936-1947, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 1716)
  - Robinson, Harold, 1942 (Box 78, Folder 1717)
  - Roche Institute of Molecular Biology, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 1718)
  - Rock Reproductive Study Center, 1961-1963, undated (Box 78, Folder 1719)
  - Romney, Seymour L., 1970 (Box 78, Folder 1720)
  - Roper, Barry W., 1966 (Box 78, Folder 1721)
  - Roscoe B. Jackson Memorial Laboratory, 1945 (Box 78, Folder 1722)
  - Rosenberg, Freda, 1945 (Box 78, Folder 1723)
  - Rosenblueth, Arturo, 1937, 1939-1940, 1942 (Box 78, Folder 1724)
  - Rosenthal, Melvin S., 1957-1963, 1966-1970, undated (Box 78, Folder 1725-1726)
  - Roth, Eleanor, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 1727)
  - Rowe, Wallace P., 1964-1965, 1969, 1972-1974 (Box 78, Folder 1728)
  - Royal Society of Health, 1956-1957, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 1729)
  - Royal Society of Medicine, 1966-1968 (Box 78, Folder 1730)
  - Royce, Stephen, 1952 (Box 78, Folder 1731)
  - Rubella, 1969, 1972-1973, undated (Box 78, Folder 1732)
  - Rubinstein, A. Daniel, 1942-1944 (Box 78, Folder 1733)
  - Ruckle, Gisela, 1953-1964, undated (Box 78, Folder 1734)
  - Russell, A. H., 1944 (Box 79, Folder 1735)
  - Russell, Frederick F., 1936-1940, 1949, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 1736)
  - Russell, Paul S., 1961-1963, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 1737)
  - Russian Virus, 1954-1956 (Box 79, Folder 1738)
    See also: box 79, folder 1744
  - Russian Virus, 1957-1958, undated (Box 79, Folder 1739)
  - Russian visitors, 1956, 1986, undated (Box 79, Folder 1740)
  - Rutgers University: microbiology symposium, 1957-1958 (Box 79, Folder 1741)
  - Rutstein, David, 1939-1941, 1956, 1961-1962, 1967, 1973, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 1742)
  - Sabin, Albert, 1951-1955 (Box 79, Folder 1743)
    See also: box 75, folder 1665
  - Sabin, Albert, 1956-1965, 1967-1969, 1981, 1984-1985, undated (Box 79, Folder 1744-1747)
  - St. Louis University. School of Medicine, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 1748)
  - Saint Paul's School, 1916, 1944-1945, 1955, 1961, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 1749)
  - Salk, Jonas, 1948-1954, 1957-1960, 1963, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1750)
    See also: box 74, folders 1653-1655 See also: box 75, folders 1656-1668
  - Sander, O. A., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 1751)
  - Sanders, Murray, 1946, 1952-1957, 1960-1964 (Box 80, Folder 1752)
  - Saturday Club, 1959-1964 (Box 80, Folder 1753)
  - Saturday Review, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 1754)
  - Sauer, Mairi, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 1755)
  - Schaeffer, Morris, 1946-1947, 1950-1959, 1963-1968, 1972, 1986, undated (Box 80, Folder 1756)
  - Scheele, Leonard, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 1757)
  - Scherer, William F., 1959-1960, 1965-1968, undated (Box 80, Folder 1758)
  - Schering Corporation, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 1759)
  - Schick, Bela, 1952-1957 (Box 80, Folder 1760)
  - Schlossberger, H., 1951 (Box 80, Folder 1761)
  - Schneider, Helene, 1960-1966 (Box 80, Folder 1762)
  - Schnitzer, Thomas, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 1763)
  - Schoenbach, Emanuel B., 1942-1945, 1950 (Box 80, Folder 1764)
  - Schoening, H. W., 1945 (Box 80, Folder 1765)
  - Schroeder, Henry A., 1959-1960, 1963-1965, 1968, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 1766)
  - Schultz, Robert B., 1953-1958 (Box 80, Folder 1767)
  - Schwachman, Harry, 1969-1970, undated (Box 80, Folder 1768)
  - Shwartzman, Gregory, 1959 (Box 80, Folder 1769)
  - Schweitzer Hospital Committee, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 1770)
  - Schwentker, Francis F., 1947 (Box 80, Folder 1771)
  - Science, 1947-1949, 1954-1957, 1961-1971, 1975, undated (Box 80, Folder 1772)
  - Science Information Exchange, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 1773)
  - Scientific Advisory Committee, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 1774)
  - Scientific American, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 1775)
  - Scientists and Engineers for Johnson, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 1776)
  - Seastone, Victor, 1940-1943, 1952, 1960-1963, 1970, 1974, undated (Box 80, Folder 1777)
  - Seideman, Roy, 1952-1956, undated (Box 80, Folder 1778)
  - Seidman, Leah R., 1941 (Box 80, Folder 1779)
  - Seiffert, G., 1953-1954 (Box 80, Folder 1780)
  - Seigler, Richard, 1967, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 1781)
  - Sellards, A. W., 1940-1941, undated (Box 80, Folder 1782)
  - Selye, Hans, 1958 (Box 80, Folder 1783)
  - Sever, John L., 1967 (Box 80, Folder 1784)
  - Sevoian, Martin, 1962-1964 (Box 80, Folder 1785)
  - Shaffer, Morris F., 1944-1945 (Box 80, Folder 1786)
  - Shannon, James A., 1955-1957, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 1787)
  - Shaper, A. A., 1954 (Box 80, Folder 1788)
  - Sharp and Dohme, 1941, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 1789)
  - Shattuck, George C., 1929, 1967, 1972-1973 (Box 80, Folder 1790)
  - Shaw, Edward B., 1955, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 1791)
  - Shaw, Herbert, 1956 (Box 81, Folder 1792)
  - Shein, Harvey M., 1959-1970 (Box 81, Folder 1793-1794)
  - Shein, Harvey M., 1972-1975, undated (Box 81, Folder 1795)
  - Shelokov, Alexis, 1950, 1953-1959, undated (Box 81, Folder 1796)
  - Sherburne, Powers and Needham, 1978 (Box 81, Folder 1797)
  - Shiga, Kiyoshi, 1954, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 1798)
  - Shope, Richard E., 1953-1954, 1958, 1961-1968 (Box 81, Folder 1799)
  - Shope, Thomas, 1972-1974 (Box 81, Folder 1800)
  - Sigel, M. Michael, 1951, 1963, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 1801)
  - Sigma Xi, 1942, 1946, 1958-1959, 1962, undated (Box 81, Folder 1802)
  - Silverthorne, N., 1947 (Box 81, Folder 1803)
  - Simmons, James S., 1936, 1941 (Box 81, Folder 1804)
  - Simmons College, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 1805)
  - Sisson, Warren R., 1961-1965 (Box 81, Folder 1806)
  - Sloan-Kettering Institute, 1952-1956, 1961, undated (Box 81, Folder 1807)
  - Sloane, Nathan H., 1958 (Box 81, Folder 1808)
  - Smadel, Joseph E., 1946-1951, 1954, 1957, 1961-1962, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 1809)
  - Small, Abraham S., 1948 (Box 81, Folder 1810)
  - Smith, A. William, 1955, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 1811)
  - Smith, Arnold L., 1973-1974 (Box 81, Folder 1812)
  - Smith, George Van S., 1946, 1950 (Box 81, Folder 1813)
  - Smith, John W., 1960-1968 (Box 81, Folder 1814)
  - Smith, Kline and French Laboratories, 1951, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 1815)
  - Smith, Margaret G., 1951 (Box 81, Folder 1816)
  - Smith, Margaret H. D., 1962, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 1817)
  - Smith, Paul K., 1949-1950 (Box 81, Folder 1818)
  - Smith, William E., 1945 (Box 81, Folder 1819)
  - Smith, Wilson, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 1820)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1956, 1959, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 1821)
    See also: box 74, folder 1650
  - Smorodinisev, Anatol A., 1948, 1959-1965, 1970, 1974, undated (Box 81, Folder 1822)
  - Snyder, John, 1947-1950, 1964, 1969-1971, undated (Box 81, Folder 1823)
  - Social Responsibility in Pediatric Research: conference, 1961, undated (Box 81, Folder 1824)
  - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine, 1946-1956, 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 1825)
  - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 1826)
  - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine, 1964-1967, 1970, undated (Box 82, Folder 1827)
  - Society for General Microbiology, 1955, 1958, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 1828)
  - Society for the Study of Growth and Development, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 1829)
  - Society of American Bacteriologists, 1947-1951, 1959-1961, 1973, undated (Box 82, Folder 1830)
  - Sonic boom
    See: box 22, folder 478
  - Soule, Malcolm H., 1944 (Box 82, Folder 1831)
  - Southwood, A. R., 1949 (Box 82, Folder 1832)
  - Spectrum, 1957 (Box 82, Folder 1833)
  - Speir, Robert W., 1962 (Box 82, Folder 1834)
  - Spingarn, Clifford L., 1944 (Box 82, Folder 1835)